covers.com 2017-10-31

# Privacy Policy | Covers.com

## We respect the importance of your privacy.

Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy applies to Personal Information of non-employee Persons who interact with Covers Media Group Ltd. that is collected, used or disclosed Covers Media Group Ltd. 

Non-employee Persons in this context includes Individuals who are viewers, readers, subscribers, advertisers, contest participants, forum members, customers, Internet users who are exposed to the media and e-commerce content of Covers Media Group Ltd. 

The Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy applies to the management of Personal Information in any form whether oral, electronic or written. Covers Media Group Ltd. reserves the right to amend this Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy from time to time. 

The application of the Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy is subject to the requirements or provisions of any applicable legislation, regulations or agreements, or the order of any court or other lawful authority. 

**Exclusions from privacy protection:** The Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy does not impose any limits on the collection, use or disclosure of the following information by Covers Media Group Ltd.: 

a) Information which is available publicly, such as a Person's name, address, telephone number and address, when listed in a directory or made available through directory assistance; 

b) Information collected, used or disclosed in the course of journalistic, literary or artistic activities; or 

c) Aggregate information that cannot be associated with a specific person, such as demographic statistics about Covers Media Group Ltd. customers, or number of visitors and average time spent on a website. 

**Purposes for Collection of Personal Information:**

Covers Media Group Ltd. has collected and collects Personal Information for the following purposes: 

a) To establish and maintain responsible commercial relations with Individuals and to provide ongoing service; 

b) To understand Individual needs; 

c) To enhance, develop, market or provide products and services; and 

d) To meet legal or regulatory requirements, including to protect or defend a legal interest, and in connection with an actual or possible Covers Media Group Ltd. corporate re-organization, merger or amalgamation with another entity, or an actual or possible sale of all or a substantial portion of the assets of Covers Media Group Ltd., provided that the Personal Information disclosed continues to be used by the entity acquiring the information either for evaluation of the possible transaction, or, on completion of any such transaction, for the purposes permitted by this Privacy Policy. 

As examples of the above: 

i) Covers Media Group Ltd. may from time to time use a Person's Personal Information to contact the Person about changes, enhancements or similar notices related to Covers Media Group Ltd. products and services; 

ii) If a Person indicated that they was interested in receiving offers or information from Covers Media Group Ltd. or certain of our selected sponsors or advertisers, Covers Media Group Ltd. may send the Person materials about products and services that Covers Media Group Ltd. feels may be of interest to the Person; and 

iii) If a Person enters a contest or other promotion offered on a Covers Media Group Ltd. website, Covers Media Group Ltd. may, under the rules of the promotion, use the Person's name and certain other information to administer the promotion, such as contacting, announcing and promoting the winners of the promotion. 

**Obtaining Consent:**

Covers Media Group Ltd. will make a reasonable effort to make sure Persons understand how their Personal Information will be used by Covers Media Group Ltd.. Covers Media Group Ltd. will obtain consent from Persons before or when it collects or uses the Personal Information. Covers Media Group Ltd. will not attempt to deceive Persons into giving consent. 

A Person's consent can be express, implied, or given through an authorized representative. A Person can withdraw consent at any time, with certain exceptions noted herein. Covers Media Group Ltd., however, may collect, use or disclose Personal Information without the Person's knowledge or consent in exceptional circumstances where such collection, use or disclosure is permitted or as required by law. 

**Note:** If any Person has any questions or concerns about Covers Media Group Ltd's privacy practices, the Person can either: 

i) Write to Customer Service - Privacy, Covers Media Group Ltd., Victoria House, Victoria Place, Eyre Square, Galway, Ireland 

ii) Provide information to Covers Media Group Ltd. through the form provided on our  feedback page . 

**Refusing or withdrawing Consent:**

Subject to legal and contractual requirements, a Person can refuse to consent to Covers Media Group Ltd's collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information about the Person, or a Person may withdraw the Person's consent to Covers Media Group Ltd's further collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information at any time in the future by giving Covers Media Group Ltd. reasonable notice, unless: 

i) The consent relates to certain information required for credit approval which a Person applies for or accepts,   

ii) The consent is otherwise required by law or iii) the use or disclosure is permitted by law or is related to the legal or regulatory requirements described herein. If a Person refuses or withdraws the Person's consent, Covers Media Group Ltd. may not be able to provide the Person or continue to provide the Person with some products, services or information which may be of value to the Person. 

**Internet Aspects:**

Personal Information may be collected when a user conducts activities on or related to all websites of Covers Media Group Ltd. (see "Covers Media Group Ltd. Companies Sites") or related to services made available on the Covers Media Group Ltd. Companies Sites. Although information collected, used or disclosed on the Internet as described below often does not constitute Personal Information (and to the extent that such is the case, then the obligations under the Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy do not extend to such information), Covers Media Group Ltd. provides the details below about Internet aspects of Covers Media Group Ltd. services for the purposes of disclosure. 

**Internet Protocol Address (IP Address)**   
When the user's web browser requests a web page from another computer on the Internet, it automatically gives that computer the address where it should send the information. This address is called the computer's "IP address." For most users accessing the Internet from a dial-up Internet service provider (ISP), the IP address will be different every time the user logs on.   
Covers Media Group Ltd. may use the user's IP Address to: 

a) Facilitate the diagnosis and remedy of a technical problem reported by the user's or Covers Media Group Ltd's technical team. 

b) Display (or allow the display by Third Party advertising providers of) more appropriate and relevant content and advertising, such as content and advertising based on the user's geographic area. 

c) Estimate user traffic from specific countries or organizations. Many IP addresses are commonly associated with Internet service providers, universities, or major corporations in specific regions or localities. Aggregate information derived from IP addresses may also be reported to advertisers. 

**Cookies**   
A cookie is a small text file, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to the user's web browser from a web site's computers and is stored on the user's computer's hard drive. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to a user's computer.   
Covers Media Group Ltd. may use cookies to: 

a) Improve the operation and performance of the Covers Media Group Ltd. services and to make Covers Media Group Ltd. services easier and more convenient to use. For example, cookies help Covers Media Group Ltd. provide more personalized services by recalling user preferences on subsequent visits (e.g. language preference). Cookies also allow Covers Media Group Ltd. to save passwords and preferences for a user so that the user will not have to re-enter them on the next visit to a Covers Media Group Ltd. website; 

b) Measure aggregate user traffic and demographic statistics related to Covers Media Group Ltd. websites and advertisements (e.g. number of users, average time spent, average age and similar statistics). This information helps Covers Media Group Ltd. to better understand when to update, change or offer new services and provides Covers Media Group Ltd. with details as to the performance of Third Party advertisements and content. This information may be reported, in aggregate form only, to Covers Media Group Ltd's current and prospective sponsors, advertisers and business partners. No Personal Information will be disclosed in such reports; 

c) Display advertisements. Covers Media Group Ltd. and Third Party advertising providers may use cookies when serving advertisements on Covers Media Group Ltd. websites. In some cases, advertisements from Third Party advertisers are delivered to users (in conjunction with Covers Media Group Ltd. services) by such Third Party advertisers, or by separately contracted advertising providers on their behalf, and not by Covers Media Group Ltd.; as such, the Third-party advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy, and users should consult the privacy policies of such Third Party advertisers. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If a user prefers, the user can reset his/her browser either to notify the user when the user has received a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. The user should understand that while Covers Media Group Ltd. do not require a user to use cookies, certain Covers Media Group Ltd. services will not function properly if a user sets his/her browser to not accept cookies. 

**Links To Other Sites And Advertisements**   
A Covers Media Group Ltd. website may contain links to other websites and services. While Covers Media Group Ltd. try to link only to sites and services that share Covers Media Group Ltd's high standards and respect for privacy, a user should understand that Covers Media Group Ltd. is not responsible for the content of, or the privacy practices employed by, other companies or websites. This Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy applies only to the Covers Media Group Ltd. services related to this Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy. 

The majority of the advertisements which are displayed in connection with Covers Media Group Ltd. services are served through one or more reputable Third Party advertisement-serving companies which deliver the advertisements to users in conjunction with Covers Media Group Ltd. services. For more information about what information is collected and how information is used by a major Third Party advertising provider click here. 

**Additional Information**   
Covers Media Group Ltd. Companies automatically collect certain information about the user's computer hardware and software. This information may include: browser type, operating system type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Covers Media Group Ltd. to operate the service, to maintain the quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Covers Media Group Ltd. Companies Sites. 

Certain Covers Media Group Ltd. services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If a user registers for or uses such services, both Covers Media Group Ltd. and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services. 

**Covers Media Group Ltd. Companies Sites**   
Covers.com   
Experts.covers.com 

**The Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy in Detail**

**Definitions**

**Collection** \- the act of gathering, acquiring, recording or obtaining Personal Information from any source, including third parties, by any means. 

**Consent** \- voluntary agreement with the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information for defined purposes. Consent can be either express or implied and can be provided directly by the Person or by an authorized representative. Express consent can be given orally, electronically or in writing but is always unequivocal and does not require any inference on the part of Covers Media Group Ltd.. Implied consent is consent that can reasonably be inferred from a Person's action or inaction. 

**Disclosure** \- making Personal Information available to a Third Party. 

**Individual** \- an individual other than an Employee who   
(a) Corresponds with Covers Media Group Ltd., including complaints and including applications for employment;   
(b) Enters an contest or forum sponsored by Covers Media Group Ltd.; or   
(c) Uses, or applies to use, the products or services of Covers Media Group Ltd.. 

**Person** \- an Individual. 

**Personal Information** \- information about an identifiable Person, but not:   
a) Information that is publicly available, such as a Person's name, address, telephone number and address, when listed in a directory or made available through directory assistance;   
b) Business-contact information, such as the name, title or business address or telephone number of an employee of an organization;   
c) Information collected, used or disclosed in the course of journalistic, literary or artistic activities; or   
d) Aggregate information that cannot be associated with a specific person, such as demographic statistics about Covers Media Group Ltd. customers, or number of visitors and average time spent on a website. 

**Third Party** \- a person other than the Person or his agent, or an organization other than a Covers Media Group Ltd.. 

**Use** \- the treatment, handling, and management of Personal Information by the Covers Media Group Ltd.. 

**Principle 1 - Accountability**   

Covers Media Group Ltd. is responsible for Personal Information under its control and shall designate one or more persons who are accountable for Covers Media Group Ltd's compliance with the following principles. 

1.1 Responsibility for ensuring compliance with the provisions of the Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy rests with the senior management of Covers Media Group Ltd., which shall designate one or more persons to be accountable for compliance with the Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy. Other people within Covers Media Group Ltd. may be delegated to act on behalf of the designated person(s) or to take responsibility for the day-to-day collection and processing of Personal Information. 

1.2 Covers Media Group Ltd. has designated a Chief Privacy Officer to oversee compliance with the Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy. The Chief Privacy Officer can be contacted at Chief Privacy Officer, 26 Monivea Park, Ballybane, Galway City, Ireland. 

1.3 Covers Media Group Ltd. is responsible for Personal Information in its possession or control, including information that has been transferred to a Third Party for processing. Covers Media Group Ltd. shall use appropriate means to provide a comparable level of protection while information is being processed by a Third Party (see Principle 7). 

1.4 Covers Media Group Ltd. has implemented policies and procedures to give effect to the Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy, including:   
a) Implementing procedures to protect Personal Information and to oversee Covers Media Group Ltd's compliance with the Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy;   
b) Establishing procedures to receive and respond to inquiries or complaints;   
c) Training and communicating to staff about Covers Media Group Ltd's policies and practices; and   
d) Developing public information to explain Covers Media Group Ltd's policies and practices. 

**Principle 2 - Identifying Purposes for Collection of Personal Information**   

Covers Media Group Ltd. has collected and collects Personal Information for the purposes set out below, and shall identify the purposes for which Personal Information is collected at or before the time the information is collected. 

2.1 Covers Media Group Ltd. has collected and collects Personal Information for the following purposes:   
a) To establish and maintain responsible commercial relations with Individuals and to provide ongoing service;   
b) To understand Individual needs;   
c) To develop, enhance, market or provide products and services;   
d) To meet legal or regulatory requirements, including to protect or defend a legal interest, and in connection with an actual or possible Covers Media Group Ltd. corporate re-organization, merger or amalgamation with another entity, or an actual or possible sale of all or a substantial portion of the assets of Covers Media Group Ltd., provided that the Personal Information disclosed continues to be used by the entity acquiring the information either for evaluation of the possible transaction, or, on completion of any such transaction, for the purposes permitted by this Privacy Policy. 

As examples of the above: 

i) Covers Media Group Ltd. may from time to time use a Person's Personal Information to contact the Person about changes, enhancements or similar notices related to Covers Media Group Ltd. products and services; 

ii) If a Person indicated that he/she was interested in receiving offers or information from Covers Media Group Ltd. or certain of our selected sponsors or advertisers, Covers Media Group Ltd. may send the Person materials about products and services that Covers Media Group Ltd. feels may be of interest to the Person; and 

iii) If a Person enters a contest or other promotion offered on a Covers Media Group Ltd. website, Covers Media Group Ltd. may, under the rules of the promotion, use the Person's name and certain other information to administer the promotion, such as contacting, announcing and promoting the winners of the promotion. 

Further references to "identified purposes" mean the purposes identified in this Principle 2. 

2.2 Covers Media Group Ltd. shall specify orally, electronically or in writing the identified purposes to the Person at or before the time Personal Information is collected. Upon request, persons collecting Personal Information shall explain these identified purposes or refer the Person to a designated person within Covers Media Group Ltd. who shall explain the purposes. 

2.3 Unless required by law, Covers Media Group Ltd. shall not use or disclose, for any new purpose, Personal Information that has been collected without first identifying the new purpose and obtaining the consent of the Person. 

**Principle 3 - Obtaining Consent for Collection, Use or Disclosure of Personal Information**   

The knowledge and consent of a Person are required for the collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information, except where inappropriate. 

3.1 Generally, Covers Media Group Ltd. shall seek consent to use and disclose Personal Information at the same time it collects the information. However, Covers Media Group Ltd. may seek consent to use and disclose Personal Information after it has been collected but before it is used or disclosed for a new purpose. 

3.2 In obtaining consent, Covers Media Group Ltd. shall use reasonable efforts to ensure that a Person is advised of the identified purposes for which Personal Information will be used or disclosed. Purposes shall be stated in a manner that can be reasonably understood by the Person. 

3.3 Covers Media Group Ltd. will require Individuals to consent to the collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information as a condition of the supply of a product or service only if such collection, use or disclosure is required to fulfill the identified purposes. 

3.4 In determining the appropriate form of consent, Covers Media Group Ltd. shall take into account the sensitivity of the Personal Information and the reasonable expectations of the Persons. 

3.5 In general, the use of products and services by an Individual constitutes implied consent for Covers Media Group Ltd. to collect, use and disclose Personal Information for all identified purposes. 

3.6 An Individual may withdraw consent at any time, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice. Individuals may contact Covers Media Group Ltd. for more information regarding the implications of withdrawing consent. 

3.7 In certain circumstances Personal Information can be collected, used or disclosed without the knowledge and consent of the Person. For example, Covers Media Group Ltd. may collect or use Personal Information without knowledge or consent if it is clearly in the interests of the Person and consent cannot be obtained in a timely way, such as when the Person is a minor, seriously ill or mentally incapacitated. 

Covers Media Group Ltd. may also collect, use or disclose Personal Information without knowledge or consent if seeking the consent of the Person might defeat the purpose of collecting the information such as in the investigation of a breach of an agreement or a contravention of a federal or provincial law. 

Covers Media Group Ltd. may also use or disclose Personal Information without knowledge or consent in the case of an emergency where the life, health or security of an individual or property is threatened. 

Covers Media Group Ltd. may disclose Personal Information without knowledge or consent to collect a debt, to comply with a subpoena, warrant or other court order, or as may be otherwise related to the legal or regulatory requirements described herein. 

**Principle 4 - Limiting Collection of Personal Information**   

Covers Media Group Ltd. shall limit the collection of Personal Information to that which is necessary for the purposes identified by Covers Media Group Ltd.. 

Covers Media Group Ltd. shall collect Personal Information by fair and lawful means. 

4.1 Covers Media Group Ltd. collects Personal Information primarily from Individuals. 

4.2 Covers Media Group Ltd. may also collect Personal Information from other sources including credit bureaus, employers or personal references, or other third parties that represent that they have the right to disclose the information. 

**Principle 5 - Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention of Personal Information**   

Covers Media Group Ltd. shall not use or disclose Personal Information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the Person or as required by law. Covers Media Group Ltd. shall retain Personal Information only as long as necessary for the fulfillment of the purposes for which it was collected. 

5.1 In certain circumstances Personal Information can be collected, used or disclosed without the knowledge and consent of the Person. (See Principle 3.7) 

5.2 In addition, Covers Media Group Ltd. may disclose a Person's Personal Information to:   
a) Another person for the development, enhancement, marketing or provision of any of the products or services of Covers Media Group Ltd.;   
b) A person who, in the reasonable judgment of the Covers Media Group Ltd., is seeking the information as an agent of the Person;   
c) Any Covers Media Group Ltd. to permit the provision of services requested by the Person, and   
d) A Third Party or Third Parties, where the Person consents to such disclosure or disclosure is required by law. 

5.4 Only those Employees of Covers Media Group Ltd. who require access for business reasons, or whose duties reasonably so require, or properly designated representatives of Covers Media Group Ltd., are granted access to Personal Information about Individuals. 

5.5 Covers Media Group Ltd. shall keep Personal Information only as long as it remains necessary or relevant for the identified purposes or as required by law. Depending on the circumstances, where Personal Information has been used to make a decision about a Person, Covers Media Group Ltd. shall retain, for a period of time that is reasonably sufficient to allow for access by the Person, either the actual information or the rationale for making the decision. 

5.6 Covers Media Group Ltd. shall maintain reasonable and systematic controls, schedules and practices for information and records retention and destruction which apply to Personal Information that is no longer necessary or relevant for the identified purposes or required by law to be retained. Such information shall be destroyed, erased or made anonymous. 

**Principle 6 - Accuracy of Personal Information**   

Personal Information shall be as accurate, complete and up-to-date as is necessary for the purposes for which it is to be used. 

6.1 Personal Information used by Covers Media Group Ltd. shall be sufficiently accurate, complete and up-to-date to minimize the possibility that inappropriate information may be used to make a decision about a Person. 

6.2 Covers Media Group Ltd. shall update Personal Information about Persons as and when necessary to fulfill the identified purposes or upon notification by the Person. 

**Principle 7 - Security Safeguards**

Covers Media Group Ltd. shall protect Personal Information by security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. 

7.1 Covers Media Group Ltd. shall protect Personal Information against such risks as loss or theft, unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, modification or destruction, through appropriate security measures. Covers Media Group Ltd. shall protect the information regardless of the format in which it is held. 

7.2 Covers Media Group Ltd. shall protect Personal Information disclosed to third parties by contractual agreements stipulating the confidentiality of the information and the purposes for which it is to be used. 

7.3 All employees of Covers Media Group Ltd. with access to Personal Information shall be required as a condition of employment to respect the confidentiality of Personal Information. 

**Principle 8 - Openness Concerning Policies and Practices**

Covers Media Group Ltd. shall make readily available to Persons specific information about its policies and practices relating to the management of Personal Information. 

8.1 Covers Media Group Ltd. shall make information about its policies and practices easy to understand, including:   
a) The title and address of the person or persons accountable for the compliance with the Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy and to whom inquiries or complaints can be forwarded;   
b) The means of gaining access to Personal Information held by Covers Media Group Ltd.; and   
c) A description of the type of Personal Information held by Covers Media Group Ltd., including a general account of its use. 

8.2 Covers Media Group Ltd. shall make available information to help Persons exercise choices regarding the use of their Personal Information. 

**Principle 9 - Access to Personal Information**

Covers Media Group Ltd. shall inform a Person of the existence, use and disclosure of his or her Personal Information upon request and shall give the Person access to that information. 

A Person shall be able to challenge the accuracy and completeness of the Personal Information and have it amended as appropriate. 

9.1 Upon request, Covers Media Group Ltd. shall afford to a Person a reasonable opportunity to review the Personal Information in the Person's file. Personal Information shall be provided in understandable form within a reasonable time and at minimal or no cost to the Person. 

9.2 In certain situations, Covers Media Group Ltd. may not be able to provide access to all of the Personal Information that they hold about a Person. For example, Covers Media Group Ltd. may not provide access to information if doing so would likely reveal Personal Information about a Third Party or could reasonably be expected to threaten the life or security of another person. Also, Covers Media Group Ltd. may not provide access to information if disclosure would reveal confidential commercial information, if the information is protected by solicitor-client privilege, if the information was generated in the course of a formal dispute resolution process, or if the information was collected in relation to the investigation of a breach of an agreement or a contravention of a federal or provincial law, or if the information was collected as part of journalistic, literary or artistic activities. If access to Personal Information cannot be provided, Covers Media Group Ltd. shall provide the reasons for denying access upon request. 

9.3 Upon request, Covers Media Group Ltd. shall provide an account of the use and disclosure of Personal Information and, where reasonably possible, shall state the source of the information. In providing an account of disclosure, Covers Media Group Ltd. shall provide a list of organizations to which it may have disclosed Personal Information about the individual when it is not possible to provide an actual list. 

9.4 In order to safeguard Personal Information, an individual or employee may be required to provide sufficient identification information to permit Covers Media Group Ltd. to account for the existence, use and disclosure of Personal Information and to authorize access to the individual's file. Any such information shall be used only for this purpose. 

9.5 Covers Media Group Ltd. shall promptly correct or complete any Personal Information found to be inaccurate or incomplete. Any unresolved differences as to accuracy or completeness shall be noted in the Person's file. Where appropriate, Covers Media Group Ltd. shall transmit to third parties having access to the Personal Information in question any amended information or the existence of any unresolved differences. 

9.6 A Person can obtain information or seek access to his or her Personal Information by contacting a designated representative at Covers Media Group Ltd. principal office. 

9.7 An employee can obtain information or seek access to his or her Personal Information by contacting his or her immediate supervisor within Covers Media Group Ltd.. 

9.8 Third parties may collect information via email/messages from Covers.com to use according to their own privacy policies. One such third party company is LiveRamp. To opt out of LiveRamp for the Covers website please click [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). To opt out of LiveRamp for the Covers App please click [here](http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices). 

**Principle 10 - Challenging Compliance**

A Person shall be able to address a challenge concerning compliance with the above principles to the designated person or persons accountable for the compliance of Covers Media Group Ltd. with the   
Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy. 

10.1 Covers Media Group Ltd. shall maintain procedures for addressing and responding to all inquiries or complaints from Persons about Covers Media Group Ltd's handling of their Personal Information. If any Person at any time has any questions or concerns about Covers Media Group Ltd's privacy practices, please contact us at:

**Covers Media Group Ltd.  
Victoria House, Victoria Place   
Eyre Square, Galway, Ireland  
Ireland**

You may contact us through our feedback page   
You may contact us by phone on 1-800-840-9677 

10.2 Covers Media Group Ltd. shall inform Persons about the existence of these procedures as well as the availability of complaint procedures. 

10.3 The person or persons accountable for compliance with the Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy may seek external advice where appropriate before providing a final response to individual complaints. 

10.4 Covers Media Group Ltd. shall investigate all complaints concerning compliance with the Covers Media Group Ltd. Privacy Policy. If a complaint is found to be justified, Covers Media Group Ltd. shall take appropriate measures to resolve the complaint including, if necessary, amending its policies and procedures. A Person shall be informed of the outcome of the investigation regarding his or her complaint.
